We
were looking for a signal
A light in the endless black A single voice in the
universe to tell us we're on the right track We
found the fire in the wild
We found the heart in the machine.
Building a dream from nothing, a sound the world
has never seen. We are the stardust engine,
racing through the night. We're burning on the
fuel of a brand new light.
♪ We are the stardust ♪ ♪ Engine, you're taking
flight ♪ ♪ Turning our future on, shining so
bright ♪ ♪
They try to ground us, keep us small ♪ ♪ Tell us
that we were gonna fall ♪ But they don't know the
things we know. They haven't seen the places
we'll go. We are the stardust engine racing
through the night. We're burning on the fuel of a
brand new light.
We are the stardust engine Yeah, we're taking
flight Turning our future on Shining so bright
We are the cosmos We are the fire We're taking
this one Higher and higher We are the stardust We
are the
angels We are the stardust Angels
We are the stardust engine, racing through the
night. We're burning on the fuel of a brand new
light.
We are the stardust engine. Yeah, we're taking
flight, turning our future on, shining so
bright.
Shine so bright.
Shine so
bright.
We're taking flight.